movieranker.com 2019-07-13

# New Movies | Movie Trailers | Theater Movies - Movie Ranker

* * *

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how Movie Ranker LLC (“ **Movie Ranker** ” or " **MovieRanker** " or " **MR** ") may collect and use the personal information you provide when using our Service. The term “Service” includes the website www.movieranker.com and its related sub-domains and subsites, MR’s related mobile device application, and any related content, software, applications, widgets, materials and/or services made available by MR. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the terms “we,” “us” and “our” refer to MR, and “you” refers to you, as a user of the Service.

This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below) and how you can access and update this information. Your use of this Service indicates that you accept our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, and consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information and other information as described in this Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings set forth in the Terms of Use.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using this Service, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to abide by this or any future Privacy Policy, do not use or access our Service.

 **Contents:**

  1. [ Scope of Privacy Policy](javscritp:void\(0\))
  2. [Information We Collect and How We Collect It](javscritp:void\(0\))
  3. [Minors and Children Under Age 13](javscritp:void\(0\))
  4. [Our Use of Your Information](javscritp:void\(0\))
  5. [Sharing Information with Third Parties](javscritp:void\(0\))
  6. [Accessing and Modifying Your Information](javscritp:void\(0\))
  7. [Protecting Your Information](javscritp:void\(0\))
  8. [California Residents](javscritp:void\(0\))
  9. [GDPR Compliance](javscritp:void\(0\))
  10. [Changes to Privacy Policy](javscritp:void\(0\))
  11. [Contact Us](javscritp:void\(0\))

##  1\. Scope of Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below) gathered when you are using or accessing the Service. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personally Identifiable Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Website”) that you elect to access through the Service or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Websites that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Websites. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Website you access.

##  2\. Information We Collect and How We Collect It 

When you use the Service, we may ask you to provide information about yourself to enable us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Service and to provide you with the services and information you request. We collect several types of information from and about you, including: 

  * information that, taken alone, identifies you and that can be used to contact you, online or offline (“Personally Identifiable Information”), which may include, for example, your legal personal or business name, legal physical address and email address; 
  * information about you that cannot be used, alone, to identify you, which may include, for example, demographic information including zip code; and 
  * information about your use of our Service, which may include, for example, internet connection, your computer or mobile device and software you use to access our Service, including your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address or other device identifiers. 

Below, we detail the specific types of information we collect from our users.

### a. _Account Information_

When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personally Identifiable Information, such as your name, username, password, postal address, and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an Account on the Service and providing Personally Identifiable Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you, and therefore, you may not be anonymous.

We may use your contact information to send you information about our Service, your Account and our business dealings. We may also use your contact information to send you promotional emails, including about our products and services. Our promotional emails tell you how to “opt-out” or “unsubscribe.” We also reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for Account recovery purposes.

### b. _User Content_

Some features of the Service also allow you to submit “User Content” (as defined in our Service’s Terms of Service). User Content may also include your Personal Information if you choose to do so (e.g., you upload your name or image to an account page or a user comment).

### c. _Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically_

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Service, including your IP address and cookie information. Generally, the Service automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Service. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Service so that we can analyze and improve them.

### d. _Information Collected Using Cookies and Web Beacons_

“Cookies” are small data files that are sent to your web browser when you access a website, and the files stored on your device’s hard drive. We use “session” cookies to keep you logged in while you use our Service, to track your preferences and to track trends and monitor usage and web traffic information on our Service. These are erased when you close your browser. We use “persistent” cookies to relate your use of our Service to other information about you and store information about your preferences to make your user experience consistent and customized. For example, we may create a persistent cookie that includes some basic information about you, like your favorite website locations and whether customer support responded to your inquiry. These cookies stay on your hard drive until you erase them or they expire and associate your information with your account even if you are logged out.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your settings on the browser settings to refuse cookies or prompt you before accepting cookies. You can also use your browser settings or other tools to delete cookies you already have. However, if you disable or refuse cookies, then certain features of our Service may be inaccessible or not function properly.

Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personally Identifiable Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personally Identifiable Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Service and may associate that information with your Account if you have one.

Certain features of our Services may use local shared objects (or “flash cookies”). Flash cookies are small files similar to browser cookies that collect and store information about your preferences and where you browse and what you look at on our Service. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser or device settings that are used for browser cookies. You may adjust your Adobe Flash Player settings to prevent flash cookies from being placed on your hard drive.

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.

We may use “clear GIFs” (aka “web beacons” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies, on our Service or in our communications with you to enable us to know whether you have visited a part of our Service or received a message. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a website or in an email or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote website on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a website or message.

We do not automatically collect Personally Identifiable Information, but we may tie Personally Identifiable Information with the automatically collected information using the above tools or information collected from other sources.

We may also log information using digital images called web beacons on our Service or in our emails. We may use web beacons to manage cookies, count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We may also use web beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails.

We do not track our users across Third Party Websites and thus do not respond to Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals. However, some Third Party Websites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, certain website browsers allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked.

### e. _Information Related to Advertising_

To support and enhance the Service, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Service. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.

Advertisements served through the Service may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category and may be based on (i) anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user, including Personally Identifiable Information, (ii) Service usage patterns of particular users, or (iii) your activity on a third party website. We do not provide Personally Identifiable Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Service.

##  3\. Minors and Children Under Age 13 

We are committed to complying with all aspects of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register on our Service. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to use or register on our Service or send any Personally Identifiable Information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any Personally Identifiable Information to MR or on the Service. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personally Identifiable Information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please send a detailed message to support@movieranker.com.

##  4\. Our Use of Your Information 

We may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personally Identifiable Information to:

  * provide to you and communicate with you about the services, content, features or products you use or request; 
  * customize and optimize the content or advertisements you receive when you use the Service, and otherwise improve your experience on our Service; 
  * complete the fulfillment of your order, including in communications with certain charities, athletes or celebrities; 
  * analyze and improve our services, which may include tracking traffic, usage, and navigation patterns related to your activities on the Service and the links we provide to Third Party Websites or advertisements; 
  * secure your Account and prevent fraud;
  * carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection; 
  * protect our or a third-party’s legal rights or interests; and
  * in any other way we may expressly disclose to you when you provide the information.

##  5\. Sharing Information with Third Parties 

We may share information that is not Personally Identifiable Information and that does not identify you personally, with third-parties or our affiliates.

We may share Personally Identifiable Information with our partners, service providers, vendors and others in order to provide you the Service you request, fulfill your order (including, for example, certain charities, athletes or celebrities), or to provide you some other product or service you specifically use or request; subject in each case to commitments by such parties to use your information only for that purpose and to protect it from disclosure. For example, we may use service providers like shopify.com to operate our online store and to process your payment information when you conduct transactions through the Service.

We may share Personally Identifiable Information in response to a valid law enforcement request or legal process, to protect our rights and property or those of third parties, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

We may share Personally Identifiable Information with a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of MR’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which Personally Identifiable Information held by MR about our Service users is among the assets transferred.

Additionally, in the following circumstances, we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information without your consent:

  * if we believe there is a serious and imminent threat to the life, health or safety of yourself or another person; 
  * to investigate or report on activity which we believe on reasonable grounds to be unlawful;
  * if disclosure is required or authorized by law (for example, in response to a subpoena or where a regulatory authority has the power to request the provision of certain records or information); 
  * if disclosure is reasonably necessary to enable an enforcement body to perform its functions, for example the prevention, detection, investigation, prosecution or punishment of criminal offenses, or the preparation for, or conduct of, proceedings before any court or tribunal, or implementation of the orders of a court or tribunal; or 
  * if we deem it necessary in our sole discretion to protect our legal and legitimate business interests.

##  6\. Accessing and Modifying Your Information 

You will have the opportunity to review and modify the information stored in your Account any time you log onto your Account using the username and password listed on the Account.

##  7\. Protecting Your Information 

We take the security of your Personally Identifiable Information very seriously, and have implemented policies and procedures, including technical measures, that are designed to help safeguard it. Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our Service, which you select at registration, should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. While we strive to use best practices to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, the Internet and computer technology is not 100% secure and we cannot absolutely ensure the security of any Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to us. 

##  8\. California Residents 

California residents may choose to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes or choose to opt out of such disclosure. Our policy is not to disclose Personally Identifiable Information collected online to a third party for directing marketing without your approval. To make a request or to opt out at any time, please contact us at support@movieranker.com or the other contact information provided below.

##  10\. Changes to Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. It may be necessary from time to time for us to modify this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations, and industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on this Service and updating the “last modified” date at the top of this page. If the changes are material, we will provide you additional, prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. If revisions to the Privacy Policy are unacceptable to you, you must cease using this Service.

##  11\. Contact Us 

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at  
support@movieranker.com or at the following address:

Movie Ranker LLC  
Attn: Registered Agent  
3773 Howard Hughes Pkwy, #500S  
Las Vegas, NV 89169
